Council, would you give them any casualties please?
I thought I was thinking for this opportunity to come and come before you and ask for guidance for our city leaders.
Thank you for our shults and for City Manager.
All these who serve so diligently guiding this direction, following this task that you can wisdom,
follow the way believe that we believe in a big God and a big way that we can do big things.
Thank you.
These students that are here tonight were thankful for any of you.
Thank you for our athletes.
Thank you for our students.
Thank you for Dr. Hale.
All the things you've done.
My campus is where it means to this community.
I follow the blessings people as they do here this this tonight.
And you just say, I pray believe in that big thing.
And then we meet with the Spawning Blackwood.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation that we are in this world with liberty and justice for all.
I don't think we'll probably begin to go to the first elections in my wish to address the authority.
Only in the agenda.
Being done.
Go to the consent agenda.
Staff is recommending on 637 and the consent agenda.
There's no doubt that we'll take a motion.
I'll approve.
A second.
Weston.
Aye.
Lewis.
The New Business Dean.
Aye.
Staff reports.
I want to go from Weston.
First take a look at the announcements.
So you can go ahead.
Thank you.
Good job.
What's your job?
Yes.